#### **CURRICULUM VITAE**

#### **PERSONAL DETAILS**

NAME: MAINA MARY WANJIKU

ID NO: 35827008

DATE OF BIRTH: 18/08/1998

TELEPHONE NO: 0713524861

EMAIL: mainamary321@gmail.com

LANGUAGES: ENGLISH, KISWAHILI

# **OBJECTIVE**

To apply my diverse skills through the application of mathematics in statistics and computing skills acquired in my undergraduate study Mathematics and Computer Science pertaining this particular this position. I intend to apply diligence, creativity and knowledge towards the success of the organization as I gain more experience to satisfy my intellectual and professional curiosity.

### **ACADEMIC BACKGROUND**

2017 – Date: Kenyatta University (Fourth year first semester)

Bachelor of Science Mathematics and Computer Science

2013 - 2016 Kahuhia Girl's High School

Kenya Certificate of secondary education (KCSE) B plus 73 points.

2005 – 2012 Race Track Primary School

Kenya Certificate of Primary Education (KCPE) 387 marks

### **SKILLS AND COMPETENCIES**

- Programming Languages: HTML, CSS, JAVASCRIPT and REACT
- Knowledge in API integration
- Skilled in data entry using SPSS and Advanced excel.
- Knowledge and understanding of TCP/IP networks.
- Microsoft azure fundamental knowledge.
- Database knowledge MYSQL
- Version control system with Git and GitHub.
- Willingness to learn and work in a fast paced and demanding environment.

# **WORK EXPERIENCE**

December 2020 to date

Organization: Lux Tech Academy

Position: Event facilitator

October 2020 to December 2020

Company: Dukaree Company

Position: Intern

May 2019 to June 2019

Company: CPS International Research

Position: Research assistant

# **REFEREES**

Eric Araka.

Lecturer CIT Department.

Kenyatta University Main Campus.

Personal Mobile 0727815187.

Email: araka.eric@ku.ac.ke.

Dave Mola.

Researcher.

Kenyatta University Main Campus.

Personal mobile 0726361268.

Email: johndave.molla@gmail.com.